let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
    answer: "Field",
    options: [
      "Report",
      "Field",
      "Record",
      "File"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Blue is what number on the resistor color code?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Changing computer language of 1's and 0's to characters that a person can understand is...",
    answer: "Decode",
    options: [
      "Highlight",
      "Clip art",
      "Decode",
      "Execute"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What's a web browser?",
    answer: "A software program that allows you to access sites on the World Wide Web",
    options: [
      "A kind of spider",
      "A computer that stores WWW files",
      "A person who likes to look at websites",
      "A software program that allows you to access sites on the World Wide Web"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "https://www.youtube.com/?gl=IN&tab=r1&authuser=0 - is an example of what?",
    answer: "A URL",
    options: [
      "A URL",
      "	An access code",
      "A directory",
      "A server"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many bits is a byte?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "4",
      "8",
      "16",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How do you subscribe to an Internet mailing list?",
    answer: "Send e-mail to the list manager",
    options: [
      "Contact your Internet service provider",
      "Send e-mail to the list manager",
      "Telephone the mailing list webmaster",
      "Send a letter to the list"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Computers calculate numbers in what mode?",
    answer: "Binary",
    options: [
      "Decimal",
      "Octal",
      "Binary",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is an FET?",
    answer: "Field Effect Transistor",
    options: [
      "	Farad Effect Transformer",
      "Field Effect Transformer",
      "Field Effect Transistor",
      "French Energy Transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The speed of your net access is defined in terms of...",
    answer: "Kbps",
    options: [
      "RAM",
      "MHz",
      "Kbps",
      "Megabytes"
    ]
  },
];